

Bence Henz

Multimedia Designer

Odense, Denmark

08/12/1993

M henzbnc@gmail.com

+45 50 11 71 14

henz.design

C2 Native

ے Profile

Experienced Freelancer with a demonstrated history of working in the graphic design industry. Skilled in Search Engine Optimization (SEO), WordPress, Web Design, and Networking. Strong professional with a AP Degree focused in Multimedia Design and Communication from Erhvervsakademiet Lillebælt (EAL).

Work Experience

Freelancer 2014 - 2018 Internet

Freelance Experience through various sites

02/2018 - 05/2018 **Graphic Design Intern**

Repair Café Odense

03/2018 - 04/2018 Kitchen Assistant Denmark

Café Skt. Gertrud

04/2017 - 01/2018 Flyer Distributor Denmark Flyeromdeling ApS

Education

AP Multimedia Design and Communication

Lillebaelt Academy

High School Diploma and Arts Magiszter Budapest Foundation 09/2016 - 06/2018

Denmark

Denmark

09/2014 - 06/2016

Hungary

28 Volunteer Experience

Student Volunteer

Lillebaelt Academy

10/2016 - 06/2018

Denmark

Student Volunteer

Tinderbox Festival

06/2017 - 06/2017

Denmark

Student Worker

2005 - 2009

Children's Railway of Budapest

Hungary

① Competencies

- Adove Creative Suite
- Google Apps
- Google Analytics
- Google Ads

- Scrum
- Wordpress
- SEO